Speaker 1: Alright, I had the opportunity to speak with the Deputy CEO for the U.S. Agency for Global Media. That is, of course, the one, the only, our good friend Carrie Lake. She's taken U.S. AGM down to the bare bones in employment in order to restore its value. But it seems that some foreign nationals, foreign nationals who are here on work visas, well, they don't hold roles in the agency anymore, but they're refusing to go home. Take a look.
Speaker 1: Eric, so tell us about these folks that you're eliminating the jobs, which is great, saving the taxpayers money, but these people, well, they're on work visas, they don't want to go home. Should they be going home?
Well, this
Speaker 2: program should have never started to begin with. We should have never been doing a J-1 visa program, bringing foreign journalists
Speaker 3: in. There's a different visa to bring journalists in, and it was a way to
Speaker 4: bring people in from many nations to work in Voice of America.
Speaker 4: and many of them from nations that are hostile to America. These are from countries that really are adversarial to the United States of America, and so you bring people in from them, and you have to worry if they will become a national security risk. Well, we've decided to stop that J-1 visa program and no longer do that. We are downsizing, I like to call it right-sizing, an agency that got way out of control. And now that we've done that, we have many of these folks who came in on the J-1 visa, which means
Speaker 3: they can only
stay
Speaker 3: as long as this job is available to them who don't want to leave and are trying to find any reason they can to stay and so we're we're going to work to make
Speaker 4: sure that they leave our country their their time here is up and i i said it before if i have to go to the airport with them and accompany them to the airport and get them on the flight i will do that but this is not a hostile and america's not a hostile you don't get to come here and stay
Speaker 5: forever when your job is up it's time to go home And that's exactly what we're pushing right now.
Speaker 6 (lower-pitched voice): I don't know. Maybe call me crazy. I was there, but maybe Alligator Alcatraz could house him for a few weeks before they get some. They may change their mind about sticking around. Just a thought, Carrie.
Speaker 7: Well, you know what? If you overstay your visa, ICE is going to find you, and they will find you in this case as well. I just like
Speaker 8: him to hang out with the Alligator
Speaker 6 (lower-pitched voice): Alcatraz for a little while, teach him a little bit about blessing. Again, you punish some bad behavior, you stop having the bad behavior, generally speaking, that is,
this other story
Speaker 6 (lower-pitched voice): But Kerry, this kind of ticks me off quite a bit, Ruben Gallega, the senator from the state of Arizona that you live in, lived in, has now done something that Adam Schiff has done and we believe Leticia James has done, used the tax code to their advantage, lied about their primary residence and got some sort of sweetheart loan and agreement deals illegally,
right?
I
Speaker 9: remember
Speaker 4: covering this, I ran against this guy in the Senate race and the media just ignored the story. When he
Speaker 3: applied for his application for a mortgage in Arizona, he said Arizona was his main residence. When he applied for one in D.C., he said D.C. is his main residence. Now, there's a couple of problems there.
Speaker 4: If D.C. is your main residence and you're lying on a federal form,
Speaker 4: then you really cannot serve the people of Arizona. You have to be a resident of the state of Arizona to be a representative, which is what he was at the time. But furthermore, it was a special VA loan that was designed to help people who were part of the military afford to buy their first home. And he used that, according to documents, to buy a nearly million-dollar home
Speaker 4: in the D.C. area and said it had to be your main residence to get that sweet deal on the mortgage. And when he did that, he basically took away, I think it was over $900,000 is what the loan was, that ability for another veteran or military member to get that money, because there's only so much money in the program, and he took it away from others who deserved it. So I think he needs to fess up and explain where does he really live?
Speaker 4: his main residence in d_c_ or is it in arizona and if you lied about that that is a crime and i think he should be investigated i think it's worse in his case
Speaker 3: that even shifts because in his case he kept that money from going to a deserving veteran
Speaker 6 (lower-pitched voice): indeed you know you know he can be
uh...
Speaker 6 (lower-pitched voice): unethical we can even call him a scum bucket if you want but we i think when you say you lie in a federal forum you've broken the law look at hunter biden he lied on his federal forum for the firearm he was going to go to jail if joe biden didn't step in and pardon his own son and they tried to crucify president trump
Speaker 1: over a similar they said he misstated the value of mar-a-lago and they tried to throw him in jail for that meanwhile you have a u.s senator doing You have another U.S. senator in California doing it, and you have the
Speaker 6 (lower-pitched voice): chief prosecutor
Speaker 6 (lower-pitched voice): to Letitia James in the state of New York doing the same thing. And the media doesn't seem to want to cover those folks. Nope,
Speaker 10: they don't. It's, you know, it's always the same.
Speaker 4: The Democrats get away with murder, and they go after the America First Republicans. And it's just, the American people, though, are onto it, and they're really sick of seeing this kind of hypocrisy. And so hopefully, I already know they're demanding it, because I'm out and about with people every day, and they're saying, when are we going to see some
Speaker 5: accountability and justice? And so I think that
Speaker 5: is coming, and I'm looking forward to it.
Speaker 11: Kerry, I love you. I wish it were true. My problem is when
Speaker 12: you were on this side, remember you were a journalist for a while? You remember, we want to see some perp. We never... I'm going
Speaker 6 (lower-pitched voice): to pound the table on this until my face is blue and the show is dead in the ground, because we want to see politicians perp walk. For some reason, they get to DC, and they can
Speaker 1: do almost anything they want to do.
Get
Speaker 1: caught, they apologize, and they walk free. Us? Hell no. We do some of the things they do. We're in jail. January 6th, I'll give you illegal stock trading. Nancy Pelosi is illegally stock trading. Her husband is as well. These folks walk when we be in jail. I want a perp walk, Carrie. I don't know. I
Speaker 13: think the reason they walk is because it's both Democrats and Republicans who are guilty of
Speaker 4: some of the same things, and so they don't want to vote to...
Speaker 4: move things forward and investigate somebody when there's a lot of people on the other side of the aisle who are guilty of the same thing. This is a corrupt, dirty town. And thank God for President Trump, but he's being met with judges who are crooked or who are trying to run the executive branch from the courts. And it's very difficult. I'm in a fight right now. We're trying to right this agency and we're getting met every step of the way by a judge
who
Speaker 4: you know, I think is politically motivated, wants to stop President Trump, wants to stop us from enacting his agenda. And we're going to continue to fight back. But we do need accountability or the people will just give up on the whole dang system. And I believe that accountability is coming. I believe you called it perp walks. I'd like to see justice is what I call it. And that means if you've been found guilty, if you've done something wrong, you're investigated and you're
Speaker 3: actually sentenced to time.
Speaker 3: And I think it's going to come starting with maybe even potentially Barack Obama. Expand
on
Speaker 14: that. That
might
Speaker 3: be the biggest bit of justice the world could see with what he's accused of doing and what he did in that coup against President Trump. I'm looking forward to seeing some justice, especially right there. And frankly, I'd like to see justice when it comes to our
Speaker 4: elections, our rigged elections dating back at least to 2020, possibly earlier. And all of
the shenanigans
Speaker 4: shenanigans in our elections across the country. We need to see justice for that. We need to see people who cheated in elections, prosecuted and thrown in
Speaker 15: jail for what they've done. Yeah, I'd love to see it. I think with what Trump arranged and figured out with the
Speaker 6 (lower-pitched voice): Supreme Court, not arranged, but figured out with the Supreme Court, there is some sort of presidential immunity that would probably apply to Obama as well. But it doesn't apply to Hillary Clinton because she was never president, much to her own disbelief. She was never actually elected president. So
Speaker 6 (lower-pitched voice): i would love lock her up let's let's start with that that would be a great perp walk because she was complicit maybe even conspiratorial in the exact thing you talk about obama kerry great having you really good to see you my friend
Speaker 16: good to be on with you as well eric and we will